<Computer id="eosPC2" name="Linda's Laptop" security="1" icon="DLCLaptop" allowsDefaultBootModule="true" ip="3154b993" type="2">

  <ports>3659, 22, 6881</ports>
  <portRemap>6881=29084</portRemap>

  <portsForCrack val="1" />
  <trace time="-1" />
  <firewall level="-1" />
  <admin type="progress"/>

  <file path="home/analyses" name="DO_NOT_LET_YOUR_KIDS_PLAY_TF2.txt">hi all

first i must say thank you all for this board so i can keep my son away from nasty stuff the devil puts on this earth

as grateful as i am i am here to tell you all to ban team fortress 2 (abbreviated as TF2) for the following reasons

i discovered about it this weekend when my 15 year old son charlie brought home his friend and they were playing on his friend's laptop a game where it's nothing but killing, bad words, god bashing, anti-american propaganda, and worst of all HOMOSEXUALITY

first off this is their artwork they use to advertise to the MASSES

as you can see, they all are posed to look threatening (i guess that's what boys like these days)

there is also blantent homosexuality (when the doctor heals his patients they all say things like "i love this doctor" or "get behind me doctor!")

they made a character that looks like a soldier and he talks about god's world being his ("this is my world, you are not welcome in my world!") when i heard this i was MORBIDLY SHOCKED and appalled and ashamed of my son and he knew it

i was wondering why my son was getting into fights and after i saw this i banned him from ever seeing his friends

if you see your child playing this, tell them to uninstall it and watch him do it!!!

hope this helps parents out so your child doesn't stray far from god!

-baseballmom67

### NOTES ###
This all reads like nonsense. Is this really how parents raise their kids today? I'm certain this must be some kind of sick parody!</file>

  <file path="home" name="journal.txt">Today Annie came up to me and asked me "why are you still a christian?"

It was an interesting question; one which I had considered easy to answer until today. I love Annie with all my heart and only want what's the best for her, but something overtook me at the time when she said that. I froze up, then I yelled at her and she ran off back to her computer, working on whatever it is she does up there.

Am I the bad person? Someone questioning something that is a fundamental part of you *should* allow you to at least respond negatively, but I feel really bad for doing that to my daughter. I'm going to make her her fav kind of dinner tonight to make it up to her. I hope she can forgive me, just as the Lord shall forgive her.

I don't know. :(</file>

  <eosDevice name="Linda's ePhone X5" id="eosIntro2" icon="ePhone2" empty="false">
    <note>shopping list
bread
eggs
milk
pasta
toilet paper
rosemary
candles
toothpaste
silverware
apples
wine</note>
  </eosDevice>

  <Memory>
   <Commands>
   </Commands>
   <Data>

   </Data>
   <Images>
     <Image>Media/MemImages/christian1.jpg</Image>
     <Image>Media/MemImages/christian2.jpg</Image>
     <Image>Media/MemImages/christian3.jpg</Image>
   </Images>
  </Memory>

  <positionNear target="eosRouter" position="2" total="4"/>

</Computer>
