<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="nutricoMail" name="NutriCo Mail" security="3" type="3" ip="522a739a">

  <ports>25, 80, 443</ports>
  <portsForCrack val="3" />
  <admin type="progress"/>

  <account username="susanhuff" password="read4you" type="mail" />
  <account username="robertcausey" password="fr8ibu" type="mail" />
  <account username="seanwhite" password="ohth3Me3" type="mail" />
  <account username="randalljones" password="monkey" type="mail" />
  <account username="NIN_INTERCEPTBOT" password="NUTRICO_IS_NASTY" type="mail" />

  <mailServer name="NutriCo" color="179, 114, 100">

<email recipient="seanwhite" sender="pr@jimsfinemeats" subject="FORMAL REQUEST: Quash NUTRICO_IS_NASTY">Hello Mr. White,

As head of public relations at Jim's Fine Meats Inc. we are formally requesting immediate and decisive action against the recent online movement "NUTRICO_IS_NASTY".

We see this as a mutually-beneficial proposition, as the movement has been damaging both your reputation and our sales numbers, due to associating with your brand in the past for providing pork stock.

Please write back to us ASAP.

~ PR
JIM'S FINE MEATS
-- GET SOME MEAT IN YOUR MOUTH --</email>

<email recipient="seanwhite" sender="susanhuff" subject="Concerns about recent protests?">Hello Sean,

I am sure you're as concerned as I am about the recent "NUTRICO_IS_NASTY" movement taking place around the network. I would wish that the rumors are not true and that we actually treat our animals properly.

It sounds way too outrageous to be true. People would be able to *taste* if there was sawdust in there, but no actual reports have surfaced. Did a hacker break into a server somewhere? Where are these (hopefully) baseless lies coming from?

RSVP,
~ Susan</email>

<email recipient="susanhuff" sender="seanwhite" subject="listen">ik your kinda new here but like, u need to be a bit more dynamic i think.

the issue is not with u but with ur attitude. nutrico prides itself on delivering high quality, nutritious foodstock. u need to stop reading conspiracies online.</email>

<email recipient="seanwhite" sender="susanhuff" subject="RE: listen">That doesn't really answer the question, Sean. Can I see the FDA approval email? You'd *have* one if the plant has been recently inspected.</email>

<email recipient="susanhuff" sender="seanwhite" subject="RE: RE: listen">mhm mhm can i see your RESIGNATION LETTER, susan?

jk jk. i will find it for u soon, but i promise okay, we haven't got anything wrong. i will even ask rob later, for real.</email>

<email recipient="robertcausey" sender="seanwhite" subject="fda???">hey rob

ur pretty good at photolab. think you can get this fda letter i found online and make it look like it was sent to us? get all the fancy letterhead and everything. raise if u do.

~ sean</email>

<email recipient="seanwhite" sender="robertcausey" subject="dude wtf">no im not going to do that. idc about raises i just want to make sure people eat well.</email>

<email recipient="randalljones" sender="seanwhite" subject="TIMESHEETS">randall,

pls make sure ur timesheets get filled in this time you didnt do them last month and it means you wont be getting paid properly</email>

  </mailServer>

</Computer>
