<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="torrentTopsite"
          name="XBC FTP Topsite"
          ip="87b62498"
          security="3"
          allowsDefaultBootModule="true"
          icon="DLCServer"
          type="3" >

  <ports>22, 6881, 21</ports>

  <portsForCrack val="3" />
  <proxy time="1" />
  <firewall level="9" solution="warez4lyf" additionalTime="-0.1"/>
  <trace time="170" />
  <admin type="fast" resetPassword="true"/>

  <tracker />

  <uploadServerDaemon name="XBC Topsite" folder="ftp" needsAuth="true" hasReturnViewButton="true" color="66, 9, 22"/>

  <file path="home/info_for_staff" name="ur_fucked.txt">Hey losers.

You don't know who I am, but just know that you're fucked.

The operators are gonna know all about this little scheme you're running here. XBC will never make another release again!

Unless, of course, you want to perhaps strike a deal... ;)

Keep in touch over dumpmail, my @ is at39jri on there

- Your Secret Hacker ;)</file>

<file path="home/info_for_staff" name="ur_fucked_REBUTTAL.txt">Hey loser.

You know that this shit leaves log files right?

Whoopty-doo, you can exploit FTP to upload shitty files into any directory you want. We've known about that for 2 decades. It's never gonna get patched because the MNC love to get their rocks off to unpatched exploits they think only they know.

Sorry to burst your bubble SeaSharp, or should we say, Christopher Sharp?

How's that for a ;) ? Provided of course you can even read this file now that we've rotated the server's password. Good luck getting past the proxy and firewall we just put up, too.

- FrameWarrior

▀████    ▐████▀ ▀█████████▄   ▄████████
███▌   ████▀    ███    ███ ███    ███
 ███  ▐███      ███    ███ ███    █▀
 ▀███▄███▀     ▄███▄▄▄██▀  ███
 ████▀██▄     ▀▀███▀▀▀██▄  ███
▐███  ▀███      ███    ██▄ ███    █▄
▄███     ███▄    ███    ███ ███    ███
████       ███▄ ▄█████████▀  ████████▀</file>

  <file path="home/txt" name="Ten_Curry_Commandments.txt">1. Thou shalt not use seedboxes.

2. Thou shalt collect no trackers beyond Cabal.

3. Thou shalt make no posts in the forum.

4. Thou shalt respect staff to their face but mock them on forums or IRC.

5. Thou shalt not accept unofficial invites.

6. Thou shalt not donate to trackers.

7. Thou shalt not invite anyone to any tracker, furthermore thou shalt not accept invites to any tracker except through official recruitment.

8. Thou shalt not hoard buffer.

9. Thou shalt not leech without seeding.

10. Thou shalt always having a big heart (for you).</file>

<file path="home/txt" name="Ten_Neon_Commandments.txt">#1 Files are files. If you can get the same shit from a lesser tracker it's not more special when it comes from a cabal one. Same shit different toilet. Take advantage of this and cross seed. Not doing so is like paying $200 at Best Buy for some shit you could get at Wal-Mart for $100.

#2 Seedboxes can be great as long as you're actually getting something out of it other than just seeding shit. Stream things you don't want to download and save. Host your personal website on it (with a vhost for fuck's sake, don't be dumb.) Run ZNC. Whatever you do get your money's worth.

#3 You don't need to kiss the ass of tracker staff but you do need to avoid them unless you have a good reason. Like Biggie said in the Ten Crack Commandments If you ain't gettin' bagged stay the fuck from police.

#4 Use your good boy voice in all tracker forums, comments, or IRC. Don't berate other users' their uploads. Do report them and laugh when they get warned or worse.

#5 If you don't want to use a seedbox have some source of content to upload. If you're dead weight you won't last long. Before you're set for life either upload or cross seed.

#6 There's nothing wrong with hoarding buffer as long as you plan on actually using it. The earlier you get the hard work out of the way the earlier you can fully enjoy the benefits tracker membership can offer you.

#7 Don't collect trackers unless you plan on actually using them. I know, it's tempting to be able to open every door. To access all the things. But these guys are serious about that one account per lifetime bullshit and if your account gets disabled due to inactivity it's up to them if it will be enabled again or not. You never know, you might need it later on.

#8 Only invite people who already know the private tracker game unless it's to some shithouse tracker like Hexic. Only accept invites from people at your level or better. If you have no contacts that know anything about this shit just disregard it and don't fuck with unofficial invites. Your life will be better for it.

#9 If you actually like the tracker and the staff donate if you feel like it. It's your money. But don't feel obligated at all to do so. Especially if you hate them

#10 Once your accounts are in good standing and you have access to everything you want get a fucking life. Stop thinking about that next tracker you want to get into and consume some of the content you got from the ones you already had. Go outside. Breathe some fresh air. Meet some people that aren't self absorbed assholes that will fill you with rage. I know you can do it!</file>

  <file path="home/samples" name="SAMPLE.nfo">▀████    ▐████▀ ▀█████████▄   ▄████████
  ███▌   ████▀    ███    ███ ███    ███
   ███  ▐███      ███    ███ ███    █▀
   ▀███▄███▀     ▄███▄▄▄██▀  ███
   ████▀██▄     ▀▀███▀▀▀██▄  ███
  ▐███  ▀███      ███    ██▄ ███    █▄
 ▄███     ███▄    ███    ███ ███    ███
████       ███▄ ▄█████████▀  ████████▀




..........................................................
..:++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++:..
..:++++++++++++++++++++Album Artist+++++++++++++++++++++..
..:+++++++++++++++++++++Album Name++++++++++++++++++++++:..
..:++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++:..
..........................................................

=>-Artist_____.NAME.
=>-Album______.ALBUM.
=>-Genre______.GENRE.
=>-Released___.RELEASE YEAR.

========================================================|

[CUE FILE DETAILS GO HERE]

========================================================|

=>-Source CD (Lossless).
=>-Channels 2 (stereo).
=>-Sample Rate 44.1 KHz.
=>-Sample Size 16 bit.
=>-Encoder libFLAC 1.3.0 20130526.
=>-Encoder Settings Compression-level-8 verify.
=>-Audio Quality Perfect (Lossless).
=>-Contains Album Art, CRC, ID Tag [Vorbis Comments].

========================================================|</file>

  <file path="ftp/OUR_RELEASES" name="Planet.Scuffle.2.2019.1080p.BluRay.DTS.x264-XBC.mkv">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="Four.and.a.half.Dogs.S02.1080p.WEB-DL.DDP2.0.H.264-AltHD.mkv">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="Cracknet.v5_069.w.DLC.ISO-SkiDcOlumn.iso">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/OUR_RELEASES" name="Plateu.Photolab.Pro.2032.v29.3.X64.Multilingual-XBC.exe">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="James.Proton.vs.James.Negatron.2002.NoCD.Crack-CoNSPIRACY.iso">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/OUR_RELEASES" name="X-SERVER.PACK.0day.2036.5.12-XBC.rar">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="Another.Stick.in.the.Mud-CoMPLEX.exe">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="WAPublisher.for.Plateu.Scribbler.v10.6.PC-VOLTAGE.dll">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="Square.Empires.RIP-CoMPLEX.rar">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="The.Lonely.Operator.S07E17.720p.HDTV.x264-YARRHARR.mkv">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="From.Insult.To.Injury.2021.FLAC.flac">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="Hand.In.Hand.2019.FLAC.flac">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="Equivalent.Exchange.2031.FLAC.flac">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="Here.We.Go.2011.FLAC.flac">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="Glass.Houses.2034.FLAC.flac">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
  <file path="ftp/WAREZ" name="All.Doubt.2018.FLAC.flac">#BINARYSMALL#</file>

</Computer>
